Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Catherine and today's show is a continuation of our series about giving a
我是Catherine，今天的节目是我们关于用英语做演示系列的延续。
presentation in English.
用英语做演示。
So we're talking about a special line of computers here.
所以我们在这里讨论的是一款特殊的电脑系列。
That's right and on this occasion we're going to compare two companies.
没错，这次我们要比较两家公司。
So we're going to try to tell everyone what the difference is between our company and
所以我们要告诉大家我们公司和竞争对手之间的区别。
the competitors.
竞争对手。
All right, so we learned a lot of great phrases and words for making comparisons in last week's
好的，我们在上周的节目中学到了很多用于比较的精彩短语和词汇。
show.
节目。
You're going to hear some of these again.
你们会再次听到其中一些。
Let's listen to the dialogue.
让我们来听对话。
Now of course with all this cutting edge technology there must be a catch, you might ask yourself.
当然，有了所有这些尖端技术，你可能会问自己，肯定有什么陷阱。
I bet the retail price will be too much for most consumers you might say.
我打赌零售价对大多数消费者来说会太高，你可能会说。
Well you'd be wrong.
嗯，那你就错了。
Yes of course the X420 is aimed at the luxury market but if you compare the price of our
是的，当然X420是针对豪华市场的，但如果你把我们领先竞争对手的价格比较一下，X420代表了极佳的价值。
leading competitors the X420 represents incredible value for money.
领先竞争对手的价格比较一下，X420代表了极佳的价值。
At only 15,000 RMB it is far more affordable and far more attractive than almost every
仅售15000元人民币，它比几乎所有领先品牌和型号都更实惠、更具吸引力。
leading brand and model.
领先品牌和型号。
So what differentiates us from our competitors?
那么，是什么让我们与竞争对手不同呢？
Well if we compare Orange's luxury MP40 range then we can really highlight some of the differences.
嗯，如果我们比较Orange的豪华MP40系列，就能真正突出一些差异。
Now of course Orange has an enviable record for producing revolutionary and top class
当然，Orange在生产革命性和顶级产品方面有着令人羡慕的记录，我必须承认MP40是一款令人惊叹的机器。
products and I must admit the MP40 is a breathtaking machine.
产品，我必须承认MP40是一款令人惊叹的机器。
However for most consumers the MP40 is simply far too expensive to consider.
然而，对大多数消费者来说，MP40实在太贵了，无法考虑。
Compared with the X420 it is more expensive and there's no doubt that considering the
与X420相比，它更贵，而且毫无疑问，考虑到X420的质量和工艺，我们在性价比上确实完胜。
quality and workmanship that goes into the X420 we really win hands down on value for
质量和工艺，我们在性价比上确实完胜。
money.
性价比。
Also if you compare the after sales service we offer I think we can proudly boast the
此外，如果你比较我们提供的售后服务，我认为我们可以自豪地宣称，我们在整个笔记本电脑领域拥有最好的客户服务设施。
best customer service facilities in the whole laptop sector.
最好的客户服务设施。
As opposed to most of our rivals we guarantee quality, we guarantee service and we guarantee
与大多数竞争对手不同，我们保证质量，保证服务，保证可靠性。
reliability.
保证可靠性。
The questions we must ask ourselves are what does the Alpha brand stand for and also how
我们必须问自己的问题是，Alpha品牌代表什么，以及我们如何与竞争对手区分开来？
can we set ourselves apart from our competitors?
我们如何与竞争对手区分开来？
The answer to both of these questions is the same my friends.
这两个问题的答案是一样的，朋友们。
Alpha stands first and foremost for quality, for excellence and for service.
Alpha首先代表质量、卓越和服务。
If we always stick to this philosophy then I'm confident that we will really be able
如果我们始终坚持这一理念，我相信我们真的能显著扩大市场份额。
to expand our market share significantly.
显著扩大市场份额。
Okay let me move on now to give you an idea of our marketing campaign for the X420.
好的，现在让我继续，给你们介绍一下X420的营销活动。
Alright we're back so now let's take a look at these phrases on Language Takeaway.
好了，我们回来了，现在让我们看看“语言小贴士”中的这些短语。
Language Takeaway.
语言小贴士。
Our first phrase comes from the very first sentence of today's dialogue.
我们的第一个短语来自今天对话的第一句话。
We heard this phrase cutting edge technology.
我们听到了这个短语“尖端技术”。
Now Marco what does cutting edge mean?
Marco，“尖端”是什么意思？
Okay so as you see in the dialogue we're talking about technology and if technology is cutting
好的，正如你在对话中看到的，我们在谈论技术，如果技术是尖端的，基本上意味着它是新的、非常现代的、你能得到的最新的。
edge, it basically means it's new, it's very modern, it's the newest you can get.
你能得到的最新的。
It's the most advanced perhaps.
也许是最先进的。
That's right.
没错。
So what's an example of a current cutting edge technology?
那么，当前尖端技术的例子是什么？
Can you think of something?
你能想到什么吗？
So for example when we talk about mobile phones that can now connect to the internet, you
例如，当我们谈论现在可以连接互联网的手机，你可以发邮件，它们有很多功能，甚至有两个摄像头和触摸屏。
can send emails, they have many features even two cameras and touch sensitive screens.
触摸屏。
This is a type of cutting edge technology.
这是一种尖端技术。
Okay it's the most new technology, the newest.
好的，这是最新的技术，最新的。
That's right.
没错。
So after that we heard another phrase, this is a bit different, this is more of a business
之后我们听到了另一个短语，这有点不同，这更像是一个商业短语。
phrase.
商业短语。
We have this retail price.
我们有这个“零售价”。
I bet the retail price will be too much.
我打赌零售价会太高。
So what is a retail price and how is it different from a regular price?
那么什么是零售价，它和普通价格有什么不同？
So the retail price is basically the amount of money that you pay for something at the
零售价基本上就是你在商店里为某样东西支付的金额。
store.
商店里。
Exactly.
没错。
So if I go to a store and I buy a computer for $1000, I know that the store, they bought
所以如果我去商店花1000美元买一台电脑，我知道商店买电脑的价格更低。
the computer for less money.
更低。
Otherwise they don't earn any money, it's a bad business.
否则他们赚不到钱，那生意就不好了。
That's right.
没错。
So the retail price is higher than the actual price, the cost of production.
所以零售价高于实际价格，即生产成本。
So retail price just basically means exactly what you said Marco, how much you would spend
所以零售价基本上就是你刚才说的，Marco，你为某样东西花多少钱，某样东西在商店里的价格。
on something, how much something costs in a store.
商店里的价格。
That's right, that's why they're called retail stores.
没错，这就是为什么它们被称为零售店。
Exactly.
没错。
Now moving on, when we're discussing the X420, this computer, Mr. Ford says that it's aimed
现在继续，当我们讨论X420这台电脑时，福特先生说它针对的是豪华市场。
at the luxury market.
豪华市场。
That means that this company would like to sell the computer in the luxury market.
这意味着这家公司想把电脑卖到豪华市场。
The luxury market is not the normal market.
豪华市场不是普通市场。
It's the market for very expensive, very beautiful, very nice things.
它是针对非常昂贵、非常漂亮、非常好的东西的市场。
Luxury items, luxury brands are very, very expensive.
奢侈品、奢侈品牌非常非常贵。
That's right.
没错。
So for example, a car such as a Mercedes Benz might be aimed at the luxury market, whereas
例如，像梅赛德斯-奔驰这样的汽车可能针对豪华市场，而像本田思域这样的汽车可能针对中产阶级市场。
a car like a Honda Civic is aimed at maybe more of a middle class market.
中产阶级市场。
Exactly.
没错。
Or in clothing, you could say Gucci is a luxury brand, whereas the Gap or something is a regular
或者在服装方面，你可以说古驰是奢侈品牌，而盖璞之类的则是普通
consumer brand.
大众品牌。
That's right.
没错。
So this is what we talk about when we refer to a luxury market.
这就是我们谈论奢侈品市场时所说的内容。
Now moving on to the description of the X420, Mr. Ford says that it's amazing quality and
现在转到对X420的描述，福特先生说它的品质惊人，
that the workmanship is very, very good.
而且工艺非常非常好。
So workmanship is related to the word work.
所以workmanship这个词与work有关。
And now workmanship means how something is made.
而workmanship指的是物品的制作方式。
Generally when we talk about luxury goods, we expect the workmanship to be very, very
通常当我们谈论奢侈品时，我们期望工艺非常非常
high quality.
高质量。
So that means that the way that these things are made is the best.
这意味着这些东西的制作方式是最好的。
That's right.
没错。
It's not going to break in one day.
它不会一天就坏掉。
Usually I think when you talk about workmanship or luxury items like this, maybe part of it
通常我认为当你谈论工艺或这类奢侈品时，可能其中一部分
is made by hand.
是手工制作的。
So this is what we talk about workmanship is how skilled that person is or how skilled
所以我们说的工艺就是指那个人有多熟练，或者他的手
his hands are to make this great piece of luxury good.
有多灵巧，才能制作出这件伟大的奢侈品。
Exactly.
没错。
So a very good example in the world of music is the Stradivarius violin.
在音乐界，一个很好的例子就是斯特拉迪瓦里小提琴。
The Stradivarius violins are very, very expensive because the workmanship is the best quality
斯特拉迪瓦里小提琴非常非常昂贵，因为它的工艺是世界音乐史上
in the history of world music.
质量最高的。
That's right.
没错。
Very good.
非常好。
So that's what we talk about workmanship.
这就是我们所说的工艺。
You can apply it to many different things.
你可以把它应用到很多不同的事情上。
But moving on to our last word for language takeaway today, another nice business phrase
但转到我们今天语言学习的最后一个词，另一个很好的商务短语
that we talk about specifically in sales is market share.
我们在销售中特别提到的是市场份额。
Now Marco, describe to me market share because I know what a market is.
现在，Marco，给我描述一下市场份额，因为我知道市场是什么。
It's where things are bought and sold.
就是买卖东西的地方。
But what is a share, market share?
但份额、市场份额是什么？
So in this case, we're talking about computers.
所以在这种情况下，我们谈论的是电脑。
So a market share is how much a company owns in the market or how much they sell in this
所以市场份额是指一家公司在市场中拥有多少份额，或者他们在该市场中
market.
销售了多少。
So for example, if we have a city of a thousand people and everyone there buys computers,
例如，如果我们有一个一千人的城市，那里每个人都买电脑，
if we sell computers to 500 people of that city, that means we own a 50% market share.
如果我们向该城市的500人销售电脑，那就意味着我们拥有50%的市场份额。
Okay.
好的。
So a market share is usually like a percentage, right?
所以市场份额通常像一个百分比，对吧？
It's a piece of this big pie.
它是这个大蛋糕中的一块。
That's right.
没错。
So everyone is always fighting for more market share.
所以每个人都在争夺更多的市场份额。
Whoever sells more has bigger market share.
谁卖得更多，谁的市场份额就更大。
So in the world of televisions, would you say that Sony has a large market share in
那么在电视领域，你会说索尼在电视方面有较大的市场份额吗？
televisions?
Probably, although I think maybe Samsung has a bigger market share or LG.
可能吧，虽然我觉得三星或LG的市场份额可能更大。
I don't know.
我不知道。
See, this is the thing with market shares is that there are so many brands in a certain
看，这就是市场份额的问题，在某个行业中有这么多品牌，
industry that everyone has maybe a little piece of the pie or maybe one has a bigger
每个人可能都有一小块蛋糕，或者某个品牌有一块更大的
piece.
蛋糕。
I see.
我明白了。
All right.
好的。
Well, that's it for Language Takeaway.
好了，这就是今天的语言学习部分。
I hope you guys have learned something there.
希望大家学到了一些东西。
We're going to be back in a moment with Fluency Builder.
我们稍后会在流利度训练环节回来。
Now of course, with all this cutting edge technology, there must be a catch, you might
当然，有了所有这些尖端技术，你可能会问自己，
ask yourself.
肯定有什么陷阱吧。
I bet the retail price will be too much for most consumers, you might say.
我打赌零售价对大多数消费者来说会太贵，你可能会说。
Well, you'd be wrong.
嗯，那你可就错了。
Yes, of course, the X420 is aimed at the luxury market.
是的，当然，X420是针对奢侈品市场的。
But if you compare the price of our leading competitors, the X420 represents incredible
但如果你比较我们主要竞争对手的价格，X420在性价比方面
value for money.
非常出色。
At only 15,000 RMB, it is far more affordable and far more attractive than almost every
仅售15000元人民币，它比几乎所有领先品牌和型号
leading brand and model.
都更实惠、更具吸引力。
So what differentiates us from our competitors?
那么，是什么让我们与竞争对手不同呢？
Well, if we compare Orange's luxury MP40 range, then we can really highlight some of the differences.
嗯，如果我们比较Orange的豪华MP40系列，就能真正突出一些差异。
Now of course, Orange has an enviable record for producing revolutionary and top class
当然，Orange在推出革命性和顶级产品方面有着令人羡慕的记录，
products and I must admit, the MP40 is a breathtaking machine.
我必须承认，MP40是一款令人惊叹的机器。
However, for most consumers, the MP40 is simply far too expensive to consider.
然而，对大多数消费者来说，MP40实在太贵了，无法考虑。
Compared with the X420, it is more expensive and there's no doubt that considering the
与X420相比，它更贵，而且毫无疑问，考虑到
quality and workmanship that goes into the X420, we really win hands down on value for
X420的质量和工艺，我们在性价比方面
money.
确实完胜。
Also, if you compare the after sales service we offer, I think we can proudly boast the
此外，如果你比较我们提供的售后服务，我认为我们可以自豪地宣称
best customer service facilities in the whole laptop sector.
我们在整个笔记本电脑领域拥有最好的客户服务设施。
As opposed to most of our rivals, we guarantee quality, we guarantee service and we guarantee
与大多数竞争对手不同，我们保证质量，保证服务，保证
reliability.
可靠性。
The questions we must ask ourselves are, what does the Alpha brand stand for and also, how
我们必须问自己的问题是，Alpha品牌代表什么，以及
can we set ourselves apart from our competitors?
我们如何与竞争对手区分开来？
The answer to both of these questions is the same my friends.
这两个问题的答案是一样的，朋友们。
Alpha stands first and foremost for quality, for excellence and for service.
Alpha首先代表质量、卓越和服务。
If we always stick to this philosophy, then I'm confident that we will really be able
如果我们始终坚持这一理念，那么我相信我们真的能够
to expand our market share significantly.
大幅提升我们的市场份额。
Okay, let me move on now to give you an idea of our marketing campaign for the X420.
好的，现在我来介绍一下X420的营销活动。
Alright, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So now, let's take a look at Fluency Builder.
那么现在，我们来看看流利度构建器。
So the first phrase I would like to look at on Fluency Builder is very important for consumers.
所以我想在流利度构建器中看的第一个短语对消费者来说非常重要。
That means people who buy things are very interested in this thing.
这意味着买东西的人对这个东西很感兴趣。
We call it value for money.
我们称之为物有所值。
That's right.
没错。
When Mr. Ford was talking about the X420, he said it represents incredible value for
当福特先生谈到X420时，他说它代表了不可思议的物有所值，
money at only 15,000 RMB.
仅售15000元人民币。
Okay, so 15,000 RMB sounds like a lot of money to me.
好吧，15000元对我来说听起来挺多的。
But he's saying that the value of the product is very good considering the price.
但他说的是，考虑到价格，这个产品的价值非常好。
That's right.
没错。
So what do you think the phrase value for money is?
那么你觉得“物有所值”这个短语是什么意思？
As you said, the quality and how much you are getting for this product compared to how
就像你说的，你从这个产品中获得的质量和数量，与你支付的
much you're paying for it is very, very good.
价格相比，非常非常好。
So the idea is it should be more expensive.
所以意思是它应该更贵。
That's right.
没错。
But it's not.
但它不是。
So the value considering the price is actually very good.
所以考虑到价格，它的价值实际上非常好。
So maybe I could say that this computer, this Apple computer, it's expensive.
所以也许我可以说，这台电脑，这台苹果电脑，很贵。
It's $1,500.
它要1500美元。
But the value for money is great because I'll have this computer for five years.
但物有所值，因为我会用这台电脑五年。
Another computer might break and I have to buy a new one.
另一台电脑可能会坏，我得买新的。
And also you can describe value for money as something good or bad.
而且你也可以把物有所值描述成好的或坏的。
For example, the same computer you can say doesn't represent good value for money.
例如，同一台电脑，你可以说它不代表好的物有所值。
So maybe you paid more than what you're actually getting.
所以也许你付的钱比你实际得到的多。
There was a bad deal.
这是一笔糟糕的交易。
That's right.
没错。
Great.
太好了。
Well, the next phrase is an interesting one.
嗯，下一个短语很有趣。
It's in this sentence where we talked about workmanship.
它出现在我们谈到工艺的那个句子里。
So Mr. Forbes described the X420 and he said it really wins hands down on value for money.
所以福布斯先生描述了X420，他说它在物有所值上毫无疑问地胜出。
That's right.
没错。
So the phrase that we're going to take a look at is hands down.
所以我们要看的短语是“毫无疑问地”。
So what does he mean when he says that workmanship for the X420 wins hands down?
那么他说X420的工艺“毫无疑问地”胜出是什么意思？
So this is a very spoken English phrase and it has nothing to do with your hands.
这是一个非常口语化的英语短语，和你的手没关系。
It means, well, I guess it could, hands down.
它的意思是，嗯，我想可能有关，“手放下”。
I'm not really sure what the literal meaning is.
我不太确定字面意思是什么。
But when we say it, we mean that something is without competition.
但当我们说它时，意思是某件事没有竞争对手。
So there is no doubt in my mind.
所以我心里毫无疑问。
This is absolutely the best in value for money.
这绝对是物有所值中最好的。
And so maybe if I say, oh, well, there are two or three computers.
所以也许如果我说，哦，有两三台电脑。
They're all nice.
它们都不错。
Nothing is hands down.
没有哪个是毫无疑问的。
But if I say, listen, this IBM computer is hands down the best on the market.
但如果我说，听着，这台IBM电脑毫无疑问是市场上最好的。
That means there's no other competition.
那就意味着没有其他竞争对手。
It is the best.
它是最好的。
So you can't really argue with that.
所以你没法反驳。
It's the best, no arguments there.
它是最好的，没什么好争论的。
No arguments, exactly.
没有争论，没错。
Hands down.
毫无疑问地。
He is hands down the best baseball player I've ever seen.
他毫无疑问是我见过的最好的棒球运动员。
Okay, very good.
好的，非常好。
Okay, so now moving on to our next phrase.
好的，那么现在继续看下一个短语。
When Mr. Ford again was talking about now the company, he said that the Alpha brand
当福特先生再次谈到公司时，他说Alpha品牌
is what does it stand for?
代表什么？
And he said that it stands first and foremost for quality.
他说它首先代表质量。
Okay, so this means you think about first and foremost.
好的，所以这意味着你想到“首先”。
This means above everything else.
这意味着高于一切。
So Alpha means a lot of things.
所以Alpha代表很多东西。
They make good computers.
他们生产好电脑。
They're a strong company.
他们是一家强大的公司。
But first and foremost, it means quality.
但首先，它代表质量。
It means that more important than any other thing that Alpha brand does, quality is the
这意味着比Alpha品牌做的任何其他事情都更重要，质量是
most important.
最重要的。
Okay, so basically what we're saying the first thing and the most important thing is quality.
好的，所以基本上我们在说，第一件也是最重要的事情是质量。
So that's what you mean when you say first and foremost.
这就是你说“首先”时的意思。
So you can say for example, when I'm looking for a car, price is the first and foremost
所以你可以说，例如，当我找车时，价格是首要的
important quality.
重要品质。
Okay, so we're talking about, you know, for Marco, the most important factor, the most
好的，所以我们说的是，对Marco来说，最重要的因素，买车的
important part of buying a car is the price.
最重要部分是价格。
That's right.
没错。
So moving on to our last phrase now, when Mr. Ford was ending this part of his speech,
那么现在继续看最后一个短语，当福特先生结束他演讲的这一部分时，
he said that we always stick to this philosophy.
他说我们始终坚持这个理念。
To stick to.
坚持。
So stick is a verb and a noun, if you're familiar with the noun, it's different from what we're
所以“stick”既是动词也是名词，如果你熟悉名词，它和我们今天
talking about today.
谈的不一样。
To stick to, remember that as a phrase, to stick to something.
坚持，记住作为一个短语，坚持某件事。
So to stick to means to continue doing it.
所以，“stick to”的意思是继续做某事。
Okay, you're going to hear this a lot when you talk about sports or even in the office.
好的，你在谈论运动甚至办公室场景时会经常听到这个表达。
I could say, listen, Marco, I don't want you to quit.
我可以说，听着，Marco，我不希望你放弃。
I really want you to stick to this project.
我真的希望你坚持这个项目。
Okay, so to continue doing, to not give up.
好的，所以就是继续做，不放弃。
Don't give up, right.
别放弃，对吧。
So you could say this to a child also, you know, I know you want to quit playing soccer,
你也可以对孩子这么说，比如，我知道你不想踢足球了，
but I think you should stick to it.
但我认为你应该坚持下去。
To stick to it.
坚持下去。
That means to continue playing, not to quit.
意思就是继续踢，不要放弃。
Okay, very good.
好的，非常好。
So it's a very nice and maybe spoken English phrase, which means continue doing, to not
这是一个很不错的、可能是口语化的英语短语，意思是继续做，不
give up, to be persuasive.
放弃，有说服力。
Right, to stick to something.
对，坚持做某事。
I want to stick to it.
我想坚持下去。
You should stick to this.
你应该坚持这个。
Okay, very good.
好的，非常好。
So a lot of phrases here.
这里有很多短语。
I think we've taken a look at a lot of things here.
我想我们已经看了很多东西。
Maybe we should go back.
也许我们应该回去。
Let's review one last time the dialogue and we'll be back in a bit.
让我们最后复习一遍对话，然后一会儿回来。
Now of course, with all this cutting edge technology, there must be a catch.
当然，有了所有这些尖端技术，肯定会有个陷阱。
You might ask yourself, I bet the retail price will be too much for most consumers, you might
你可能会问自己，我打赌零售价对大多数消费者来说太贵了，你可能会
say.
说。
Well, you'd be wrong.
嗯，你错了。
Yes, of course, the X420 is aimed at the luxury market.
是的，当然，X420 是针对奢侈品市场的。
But if you compare the price of our leading competitors, the X420 represents incredible
但如果你把我们主要竞争对手的价格比较一下，X420 代表了令人难以置信的
value for money.
性价比。
At only 15,000 RMB, it is far more affordable and far more attractive than almost every
仅售 15,000 元人民币，它比几乎所有
leading brand and model.
领先品牌和型号都更实惠、更具吸引力。
So what differentiates us from our competitors?
那么，我们与竞争对手的区别在哪里？
Well, if we compare Orange's luxury MP40 range, then we can really highlight some of the differences.
嗯，如果我们比较 Orange 的豪华 MP40 系列，就能真正突出一些差异。
Now of course, Orange has an enviable record for producing revolutionary and top class
当然，Orange 在推出革命性和顶级
products.
产品方面有着令人羡慕的记录。
And I must admit, the MP40 is a breathtaking machine.
我必须承认，MP40 是一款令人惊叹的机器。
However, for most consumers, the MP40 is simply far too expensive to consider.
然而，对大多数消费者来说，MP40 实在太贵了，难以考虑。
Compared with the X420, it is more expensive and there's no doubt that considering the
与 X420 相比，它更贵，而且毫无疑问，考虑到
quality and workmanship that goes into the X420, we really win hands down on value for
X420 的质量和工艺，我们在性价比上真的
money.
完胜。
Also, if you compare the after sales service we offer, I think we can proudly boast the
此外，如果你比较我们提供的售后服务，我认为我们可以自豪地宣称
best customer service facilities in the whole laptop sector.
我们在整个笔记本电脑领域拥有最好的客户服务设施。
As opposed to most of our rivals, we guarantee quality, we guarantee service, and we guarantee
与我们大多数竞争对手不同，我们保证质量，保证服务，保证
reliability.
可靠性。
The questions we must ask ourselves are, what does the Alpha brand stand for?
我们必须问自己的问题是，Alpha 品牌代表什么？
And also, how can we set ourselves apart from our competitors?
还有，我们如何与竞争对手区分开来？
The answer to both of these questions is the same, my friends.
朋友们，这两个问题的答案是一样的。
Alpha stands first and foremost for quality, for excellence, and for service.
Alpha 首先代表质量、卓越和服务。
If we always stick to this philosophy, then I'm confident that we will really be able
如果我们始终坚持这一理念，那么我相信我们真的能够
to expand our market share significantly.
显著扩大市场份额。
Okay, let me move on now to give you an idea of our marketing campaign for the X420.
好的，现在让我继续介绍我们为 X420 制定的营销活动。
Alright so that's all the time we have for today on this series.
好的，这就是我们本系列今天的所有内容。
Be sure to check out the next part next week where we're going to continue talking about
请务必在下周查看下一部分，我们将继续讨论
presentations and as you can see it's very business oriented but you can apply everything
演示，正如你所见，它非常商务导向，但你可以将学到的所有内容
that you learn to other situations as well.
应用到其他场景中。
Exactly, these phrases like hands down and to stick to, these aren't business phrases,
没错，像“hands down”和“to stick to”这样的短语，它们不是商务短语，
these are words you can use in business but I use these in my everyday life and I think
是可以在商务中使用的词，但我在日常生活中也使用它们，我认为
that with a little bit of practice you guys can sound really, really fluent in English
只要稍加练习，你们就能说得非常非常流利的英语，
and these phrases are a good place to start.
这些短语是一个很好的起点。
That's right.
没错。
So if you have any questions, any doubts or comments, you can visit our website EnglishPod.com
所以，如果你有任何问题、疑问或评论，可以访问我们的网站 EnglishPod.com，
where we'll be there.
我们会在那里。
See you guys soon.
再见。
Bye.
拜。
Okay that was great.
好的，太棒了。